Finding Aid to the Gloria Steinem papers SSC.MS.00237
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS, 1940s-90s
  This series contains photographic images of Steinem, her family, friends, and her colleagues. Several folders contain photographs of Gloria Steinem alone, from the 1940s to the present. A handful of family photographs from Steinem's childhood are located here, as well as several folders of photographs, arranged alphabetically by subject, of friends and associates; these may or may not include Steinem. Group photos are largely arranged chronologically by decade. Groups of photographs taken at specific events, such as the rally supporting the Louisiana Sugar Cane Workers, are filed separately. There are also photographs of Steinem with fans, at book signings and other such events, scattered throughout SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE -Public Response Mail. For other photos of Steinem, researchers may wish to consult Dori Jacobson's Women's Rights Portfolio, 1979-1986, also housed in the Sophia Smith Collection. Finally, there are several photographs housed in SERIES X. OVERSIZE MATERIAL, some of which duplicate images in SERIES VIII.
  - Gloria Steinem alone
    - 1940-59 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - 1960-69 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Undated 1960s (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Early 1970s [rectangular glasses] (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Early-mid 1970s [aviator glasses] (Box 214, Folder 5-7)
    - Early-mid 1970s [large oval glasses] (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Mid-late 1970s [rimless glasses, no bar across top] (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Undated 1970s [no glasses] (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - Late 1970s-early 1980s [rimless glasses with bar across top] (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - 1980s-90s [no glasses] (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - 1980-92 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - Family (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - Friends and associates
    - Individuals
      - A-B: Laila Abou-Saif, Bella Abzug, Alan Alda, Julian Bond, George Burns, Jane Byrne (Box 215, Folder 4)
      - C-D: Pat Carbine, Dick Cavett, Carol Channing, Cesar Chavez, Michele Chevalier, Marie Claire Chevalier, Karen Clark, "Crazy Alice" the cat, Guria Molina de Pute, David Dinkins, Phil Donahue (Box 215, Folder 5)
      - E-F: Brenda Feigen Fasteau, Clay Felker, Nina Finkelstein, Roberta Flack, Jane Fonda, Betty Friedan, Kristina Friehl (Box 215, Folder 6)
      - G-L: George Hirsch, Delores Huerta, Dorothy Pitman Hughes, Keizeh Iwamato, Jill Johnston, Judith Kaplan, Florynce Kennedy, Dorothy Kenyon, Linda Lavin (Box 215, Folder 7)
      - M-R: Norman Mailer, George McGovern, Shirley MacLaine, Nancy Merrill, Kate Millett, Mike Nichols, Eleanor Holmes Norton, Kian Nuwdin, Bob Packwood, Arthur Pardoll, Letty Cottin Pogrebin, Stan Pottinger, Chita Rivera, Carmen Romero (Box 216, Folder 1)
      - S-Z: Betty Schlein, Pat Schroeder, Margaret Sloan, Paul Stooky, Crystal Lee Sutton, Frank Thomas, Marlo Thomas, Sheila Tobias, Edie Van Horn, Barbara Walters, Mort Zuckerman (Box 216, Folder 2)
      - Unidentified individuals (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - Groups
      - 1960-69 Lauren Bacall, Jimmy Breslin, Clay Felker, Milton Glaser, George Hirsch, Norman Mailer, George McGovern, Gabe Pressman, Tom Wolfe (Box 216, Folder 4)
      - 1970-79 Bella Abzug, Alan Alda, Candice Bergen, Dick Gregory, Kate Millett, Holly Near, Margaret Sloan, Lily Tomlin (Box 216, Folder 5)
      - Undated circa 1970s Bella Abzug, Pat Carbine, Jimmy Carter, Dick Cavett, Brenda Feigen Fasteau, Nina Finkelstein, Roberta Flack, Jill Johnston, Florynce Kennedy, Frances Lear, Suzanne Levine, Olga Madar, Shirley MacLaine, Kate Millett, Gordon Parks, Letty Cottin Pogrebin, Stan Pottinger, Martha Shelley, Marlo Thomas, Mary Travers, Edie Van Horn, Martha Vernon, Barbara Walters (Box 216, Folder 6)
      - 1980-89 Pat Carbine, Phil Donahue, Betty Friedan, Coretta Scott King, Suzanne Levine, Bob Packwood, Stan Pottinger, Liz Smith, Mary Thom, Marlo Thomas, Barbara Walters (Box 216, Folder 7)
      - Undated circa 1980s Alan Alda, Bella Abzug, David Dinkins, John Kenneth Galbraith, George McGovern (Box 216, Folder 8)
      - Unidentified, 1950s-80s (Box 217, Folder 1-5)
        [See also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE-Public response mail: photographs of Steinem are attached to the following correspondence: circa 1973; 23 Sep 1983; Oct 1983; 9 Dec 1983; 18 Dec 1983; 3 Jun 1984; 19 Jun 1984; 1 Dec 1984; 1984, n.d.]
  - Subjects and events
    - Demonstrations, 1960s-80s (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - Gleitsman Foundation talk, undated (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - India, 1950s (Box 217, Folder 8)
    - Louisiana Sugar Cane Workers Campaign, early 1980s (Box 217, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous appearances, interviews, events, 1960s-1970s (Box 217, Folder 10-12)
    - Miscellaneous appearances, interviews, events (cont'd), 1980s-1990s (Box 218, Folder 1-2)
    - Ms. magazine: includes Elizabeth Forsling Harris, Brenda Feigen Fasteau, Pat Carbine, 1970s-80s (Box 218, Folder 3-5)
    - New York magazine, 1960s (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - Steinem speaking, 1970s-80s (Box 218, Folder 7-9)
    - United Nations photos of women working, 1958-1973 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous and unidentified (Box 219, Folder 2-3)
  - Oversize (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Contact sheets and slides (Box 219, Folder 5-6)
  - Negatives (Box 219, Folder 7)
- SERIES IX. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIAL, 1969-84
  The audiovisual materials in the Steinem papers include a range of formats: Audiotapes (cassette and reel-to-reel), Computer diskettes, Record albums, and Videotapes. Audiotapes include programs of which Steinem was the subject, interviews conducted by Steinem, and music, some of which contain feminist anthems submitted by fans. Several tapes contain interviews conducted by Steinem in connection with the ABC series "In Conversation With.. .". Audiotapes are numbered continuously by format. Use copies have been made of some original audiovisual materials. Researchers interested in viewing or listening to audiovisual materials for which there is no use copy should contact the Sophia Smith Collection to discuss options.
  - Audio recordings
    - "In Conversation with...," circa, 1982-84
      - Boggs, Lindy (Box 220, Folder 1)
        [CD available for research use]
      - Brown, Helen Gurley (Box 220, Folder 2)
      - Donahue, Phil (Box 220, Folder 3)
      - Ford, Betty (Box 220, Folder 4-5)
      - Gandhi, Indira (Box 220, Folder 6)
      - Jagger, Bianca (Box 220, Folder 7)
      - King, Coretta Scott (Box 220, Folder 8)
      - Midler, Bette (Box 220, Folder 9)
      - Ride, Sally (Box 220, Folder 10)
      - Thomas, Marlo (Box 220, Folder 11-12)
      - Walker, Alice (Box 220, Folder 13)
    - Interviews by Steinem
      - Laila Abou-Saif, undated (Box 220, Folder 14-15)
      - Koryne Horbal; also, conversation between unidentified women, undated (Box 220, Folder 16-17)
      - Glenda Jackson, undated (Box 221, Folder 18)
      - Estelle Parsons, Critics Circle Program, 13 Aug 1981 (Box 221, Folder 19)
    - Interviews of Steinem
      - Dick Pomerantz, KSTP, Minneapolis, 23 Sep 1983 (Box 221, Folder 20)
      - Harry Sobel, "The Thought Process," WRKO, 14 Sep 1983 (Box 221, Folder 21-22)
      - Joan McGrath Show, 22 Sep 1984 (Box 221, Folder 23)
      - Interview by Louise (Lucy) Knight (includes transcript), 4 Apr 2000 (Box 221, Folder 23a)
      - Gus Tyler, "Working Papers-with Gus Tyler," (topic: Outrageous Acts and Everyday Rebellions), undated (Box 221, Folder 24)
      - "New York Now," radio talk show, undated (Box 221, Folder 25-26)
      - Unknown interviewer, undated (Box 221, Folder 27)
      - Steinem and Carol Kleiman interviewed by Dianne Smith, "Relating to Women," Chicago, undated (Box 221, Folder 28)
    - Ms. magazine
      - Scott Morrison interview with Ms. magazine staff on 1st anniversary, 1973 (Box 221, Folder 28a)
        [duplicate of reel-to-reel #6]
      - Pat Carbine and Steinem discussing Ms. circulation, 1974 (Box 221, Folder 29)
      - Betty Friedan, press conference 1976?, side 2: meeting of Ms. staff [?], including Steinem [?] and Letty Cottin Pogrebin (Box 221, Folder 30)
      - Unidentified person discussing Ms., includes clips from Steinem, 1982 (Box 221, Folder 31)
      - Steinem, "1984 CAMPUS TIMES" promo and October 1984 Ms. radio magazine programs (Box 221, Folder 32)
      - Ms. Magazine interviews: A. Gloria Steinem, B. Robert Gould, C. Billie Jean King, undated (Box 221, Folder 33)
    - Moving Beyond Words, audiobook on 4 cassettes, read by G. Steinem, 1994 (Box 221, Folder 33a-d)
    - Talks by Steinem
      - "Women as a Political Force," 2 May 1972; Side B: Panel discussion: "Corporate Responsibility," Oral Luper and Richard Stoner, 3 May 1972 (Box 221, Folder 34)
      - "Know Your Market: What's Really Happening to Women Today," 55th Annual Conference of the Direct Mail Advertising Association, Chicago, 8-11 Oct 1972 (Box 222, Folder 35)
      - "73 for 73," WHN-NY, includes songs and radio show 1 Jan 1973 [?] (Box 222, Folder 36)
      - Steinem and Margaret Sloan, Staten Island Community College, 27 Feb 1973 (Box 222, Folder 37)
      - "Women for Change," intro by Maura McNeil, reaction panel to Steinem speech, 22 Feb 1974 (Box 222, Folder 38-39)
      - Public Affairs Luncheon, topic: equality of the sexes, 17 Jun 1974 (Box 222, Folder 40)
      - Lecture and question and answer session at NYU, 17 Oct 1974 (Box 222, Folder 41-42)
      - "Women in Public Life," Texas, 9 Nov 1975 (Box 222, Folder 43)
      - "Revolutionary Feminism" and "Feminism and Work," panel of Steinem, Frances Lear, Aileen Maris, Bermuda 28 Mar-3 Apr 1976 Cassette audiotapes (Box 222, Folder 44-45)
      - Steinem, Daniel P. Moynihan, and William M. Ellinghaus questions and answers, 28th Annual Business Conference of New Jersey 1976 [?] (Box 222, Folder 46-49)
      - Talk on recent travel to India 1976 [?] (Box 222, Folder 50)
      - "Families in the 80s," Southern Methodist University, Dallas, 12 Sep 1979 (Box 222, Folder 51)
      - Unidentified event, introduction by Frances Lear, 15 Jul 1979 (Box 223, Folder 52)
      - Talk in Louisiana[?] on women and politics, 1980 (Box 223, Folder 53)
      - Steinem, Erica Jong, and Louis Auchincloss panel, introduction by Olivia Dernier, 18th Century Women Symposium, Metropolitan Museum, 29 Apr 1982 (Box 223, Folder 54)
      - Steinem, Estelle Ramey, Pauli Murray, and Eleanor Holmes Norton, 1983 Conference for Women Educators, Phillips Exeter Academy, 23-25 Jun 1983 (Box 223, Folder 55-58)
      - Address at National Women's Political Caucus Convention, San Antonio, 9 Jul 1983 (Box 223, Folder 59-60)
      - Minneapolis Public Radio, 23 Sep 1983 (Box 223, Folder 61)
      - "Women of the 80s-the 2nd Wave," Oklahoma State University, 14 Mar 1984 (Box 223, Folder 62-63)
      - Speech on women's liberation, introduction by Barbara Boxer, Marin College, 1974 (Box 223, Folder 64-65)
      - "Women Update," Immaculate Heart, undated (Box 223, Folder 66)
      - Steinem and Elizabeth Reed, United Nations panel, undated (Box 223, Folder 67)
        [have preservation master; need use copy]
      - "On Self Esteem,", 13 Nov 1992 (Box 223, Folder 68)
      - "Gloria Steinem at the Great Hall, Sydney U.", 25 May 1987, 13 Nov 1992 (Box 223, Folder 68a)
    - Others
      - Holly Near, Columbia University, 7 Oct 1973 (Box 224, Folder 69)
      - Betty Friedan interview [with Phil Donahue?], discusses Steinem and the CIA 1976 [?] [poor sound quality] (Box 224, Folder 70)
      - "Anti-Defamation League Dinner Honoring Steve Kelly,", 8 Dec 1977 (Box 224, Folder 71)
      - D. Clancy reading Barbara Mikulski's talk, Bella Abzug, Democratic Task Force, 13 Jul 1979 (Box 224, Folder 72)
      - Tape sent by Dolores Brogan re: offensive statement made by USC professor, 6 Nov 1979 (Box 224, Folder 73)
    - Panel: Skip Branch, Al Church, Bill Wisner, Ted Wilson, "Men's Celebration," Women's Conference, University of Utah, 24 Oct 1981 (Box 224, Folder 74)
      - Catharine MacKinnon, Phyllis Schlafly, Stanford, 26 Jan 1982 (Box 224, Folder 75-76)
      - Dr. Krister Stendahl, "Bible Translation and the Overcoming of Sexism," for NOW, OSU, 13 Apr 1982 (Box 224, Folder 77)
      - Diane and John Rehm, "Dependence and Independence in Marriage," WAMU-FM, 23 Apr 1983 (Box 224, Folder 78-79)
      - Sarah Weddington, Women's Council Program, OSU, 8 Feb 1983 (Box 224, Folder 80)
      - Deborah K. Bright, "Achieving Successful Performance," Listen and Learn program, 1983 (Box 224, Folder 81)
      - Rosabeth Moss Kanter, Ph. D., "The Change Masters," Listen and Learn program, 1983 (Box 224, Folder 82)
      - Art Buchwald, "You ask...Buchwald Answers," Listen and Learn program, 1983 (Box 224, Folder 83)
      - "Gay liberation" and Naomi Weisstein and Bella Abzug, Feminist Press fundraiser, New York, undated (Box 224, Folder 84)
      - Tapes enclosed with public response mail
        - "A Copy for Judge Nevill", 26 Mar 1979 (Box 224, Folder 85)
        - "Attention Please, Ms. Steinem", 14 Jul 1980 (Box 224, Folder 86)
        - CPI news, Joyce DeSpain, 10 Feb 1984 (Box 225, Folder 87)
        - "Tap Is Here to Stay," Rosie Radiator, 13 May 1984 (Box 225, Folder 88)
        - "Hitler and Church", 26 Oct 1984 (Box 225, Folder 89)
        - "Torch Song," Terry Hess, 1984 (Box 225, Folder 90)
        - Virginia Lewis, 1 Nov 1989 (Box 225, Folder 91)
      - Music
        - WBAI, unidentified interview, music, 13 Jul 1982 (Box 225, Folder 92)
        - Mary Noel, songs: "Mother" and "Cinderella's Story", 1982 (Box 225, Folder 93)
        - Tyler, "Man Smart/Woman Smarter", May 1985 (Box 225, Folder 94)
        - Jerianne Garber, songs (Box 225, Folder 95)
        - Margaret M. Shelton, "The Committee Woman" (Box 225, Folder 96)
        - Ron Wallace, "Best Friend" (Box 225, Folder 97)
  - Computer diskette(3 1/2 in), Revolution from Within (Box 225)
  - Reel-to-reel audiotapes
    - Steinem
      - "The Stock Market Observer,", 22 May 1969 (Box 225, Folder 1)
      - Steinem "Women as a Political Force," and panel discussion on corporate responsibility 2 May 1972 [duplicate of audio cassette 34] (Box 225, Folder 2)
      - Guest commentator on WHN New York, 2; 4; 6 Oct 1972 (Box 225, Folder 3)
      - At American Manufacturer's Association, introduction by Fred Rice of Capitol Records (who presents her with Helen Reddy Gold Record), 9 May 1973 (Box 225, Folder 4-5)
      - Scott Morrison interview with Ms. staff on its first anniversary, 1973 (Box 225, Folder 6)
        [see audiocassette 28a]
      - Marin College speech, introduction by Barbara Boxer, 1974 [duplicate of audio cassettes 64-65] (Box 226, Folder 7-8)
      - "Focus '74," commentator introduces excerpts from Marin College speech, 1974 (Box 226, Folder 9)
      - UUWF Press Conference, award to Ms. Magazine, includes Steinem, Elinor Guggenheimer, Drusilla Cummins, Mary Daly, Pat Carbine, Steinem, Karen Decrow, Sally Preisand, 25 Jun 1974 (Box 226, Folder 10)
      - "It's About Time,", 17 Oct 1975 (Box 226, Folder 11)
      - Ms. Magazine interviews: Gloria Steinem, Robert Gould, Billie Jean King undated [duplicate of audio cassette 33] (Box 226, Folder 12-13)
      - Steinem at Erma Henderson tribute, 1980s (Box 226, Folder 14)
    - Other
      - Barbara Chopyak, audition tapes (Box 226, Folder 15-17)
  - Record albums: Steinem on the "The Helen Hall Show,", undated (Box 227)
  - Videotapes
    [See AV database for complete list]
    - Steinem
      - Film of Steinem, other person (poor quality) undated [8mm film and VHS research copy] (Box 228, Folder 1)
      - Film of Steinem, others at farm (poor quality) undated [8mm film and VHS research copy] (Box 228, Folder 2)
      - Interview, NHK News Wide (Japanese) 8 June 1985 [original VHS and DVD research copy] (Box 228, Folder 3)
      - Interview, NHK Cultural Journal (Japanese) 21 June 1985 [original VHS and DVD research copy] (Box 228, Folder 4)
      - Lecture, ESPRIT Be Informed Lecture Series, San Francisco, CA 29 April 1992 [original VHS and DVD research copy] (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - Other
      - Diane Conn, "After A Suicide,", 1994 (Box 228, Folder 6)
      - "Menopause: Dispelling the Myths, Telling the Truths, Exploring the Possibilities," circa, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 7)
- SERIES X. OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  Fans, friends, and organizations presented posters and artwork, often depicting Steinem, to her as gifts. These objects, which include an oil portrait, a pastel drawing, a hologram, and homemade plaques and pictures, are gathered together in this series along with photographs, posters, awards and citations, galleys and printed material. A Brownie beanie given to Steinem by Rita Mae Brown is among the oversize memorabilia.
  - Photographs of Steinem alone and with others (includes Jane Fonda, Dorothy Pitman Hughes) (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - Awards, tributes (includes honorary degree from University of Toledo) (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - Professional material (includes posters for speeches, advertisements, book jackets) (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - Miscellany (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - Marilyn master galleys (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - Wonder Woman (includes comic books, miscellany) (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - Artwork from friends and fans (Box 230, Folder 3)
  - Pop Show (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - Memorabilia
    - Campaign buttons: David Dinkins, Mailer/ Breslin (Box 231)
    - Ms. keychain (Box 231)
    - Simmons College mirror, 1994 (Box 231)
    - Votes for Women pennant (Box 231)
    - Hood from University of Toledo[?], 1983 (Box 231)
    - Brownie cap from Rita Mae Brown (because Steinem was never a Brownie) (Box 231)
    - Varsity letter "W,", 1948 (Box 231)
    - Wages for Housework potholder (Box 231)
    - T-shirts
      - "Ms. Holly Near Racing for Equality" (Box 231)
      - "Run Pat Run" (Box 231)
  - Awards and memorabilia: objects
    [For descriptions, see SERIES I: BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIAL-Awards, honorary degrees, and gifts]
    - Director's Guild of America, 1968 (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Penney-Missouri Award, 1970 (Box 232, Folder 2)
    - Ms. gavel, 1972 (Box 232, Folder 3)
    - Hasty Pudding Club, 1973 (Box 232, Folder 4)
    - Statuette from Marilee Dougherty, 1975 (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - ACLU of Southern California, 1975 (Box 232, Folder 6)
    - More International Seminar, 1978 (Box 232, Folder 7)
    - Leadership Award, 1979 (Box 232, Folder 8)
    - APPM stein, 1979 (Box 232, Folder 9)
    - March of Dimes, 1980 (Box 232, Folder 10)
    - Liberty Bell presented by [Philadelphia?] mayor William J. Green, 1982 (Box 232, Folder 11)
    - Charisma Award, 1982 (Box 232, Folder 12)
    - WSAAA paperweight, 1984 (Box 232, Folder 13)
    - Avon Sports Foundation, 1985 (Box 232, Folder 14)
    - Human Rights Campaign Fund, 1985 (Box 232, Folder 15)
    - CBS, "In appreciation of 'An American Portrait,'", 1985 (Box 232, Folder 16)
    - Atlanta Advertising Club, 1985 (Box 232, Folder 17)
    - Lambda Legal Defense Fund, 1989 (Box 233, Folder 18)
    - Women's Project, 1989 (Box 233, Folder 19)
    - Manhattan Award, 1989 (Box 233, Folder 20)
    - William O. Douglas Award, 1985 (Box 233, Folder 21)
    - Federal Women's Program, 1984 (Box 233, Folder 22)
    - Police Athletic League, 1990 (Box 233, Folder 23)
    - Brooklyn Chamber of Commerce, 1992 (Box 233, Folder 24)
    - YWCA, 1992 (Box 233, Folder 25)
    - Women's Hall of Fame, 1993 (Box 233, Folder 26)
    - Attorney General of Ohio, 1994 (Box 234, Folder 27)
    - NoNonsense, 1995 (Box 234, Folder 28)
    - Family Planning Council, 1995 (Box 234, Folder 29)
    - Parenting Magazine, 1995 (Box 234, Folder 30)
    - Cesar Chavez Award, 1996 (Box 234, Folder 31)
    - NWPC, 1997 (Box 234, Folder 32)
    - Key to Nashua, New Hampshire (Box 234, Folder 33)
    - Key to Kansas City, Missouri (Box 234, Folder 34)
    - Key to Dallas, Texas (Box 234, Folder 35)
    - Detroit recognition (Box 234, Folder 36)
    - LIFE (Box 234, Folder 37)
    - Roe v. Wade (Box 234, Folder 38)
    - Advertising Times (Box 234, Folder 39)
    - City of Baltimore (Box 234, Folder 40)
  - Awards and memorabilia: plaques
    - Steinem on cover of Today's Chiropractic, 1996 (Box 235)
    - SER, "For her dedication to the Ms. Foundation,", undated (Box 235)
    - I'm Every Woman Award from NYU Women's Herstory Month Committee, 1993 (Box 235)
    - National Gay Rights Advocates, 1987 (Box 235)
    - CUNY Women's Coalition Women of Excellence Award, 1986 (Box 235)
    - School of Education, Health, Nursing and Arts Professions of New York University Creative Leadership Award, 1985 (Box 235)
    - Womens Way Lucretia Mott Award, 1982 (Box 235)
    - American Marketing Association, Southern California Chapter, 1979 (Box 235)
    - Harvard Business School Class of, 1949; 1979 (Box 235)
    - American Humanist Association Humanist Pioneer, 1978 (Box 235)
    - Women's Equity Action League, 1978 (Box 235)
    - Steinem on cover of San Antonio Saturday Express-News, 1975 (Box 235)
    - More International Cultural Seminar, 1978 (Box 236)
    - American Civil Liberties Union of New Jersey, 1977 (Box 236)
    - Wonder Woman, 1973 (Box 236)
    - United States Customs Service, 1997 (Box 236)
    - Federation of Child Care Centers of Alabama, 1995 (Box 236)
    - Senate of Alabama Resolution recognizing and welcoming Steinem 1995 Key to city of Longview, Texas, 1985 (Box 236)
    - Women's International Center Living Legacy Award, 1985 (Box 236)
    - Manhattan's Woman of Vision, Manhattan Awards, 1993 (Box 236)
    - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, Emmy Award Nomination to Steinem, et al., writers of "That Was the Week That Was,", 1964-65 (Box 236)
    - "To Be Great Is to Assume Great Concerns" painting and photo of Steinem and unidentified woman, by(?) Jer Garstofsky, 1970 (Box 236)
    - Sales and Marketing Executives of Memphis, 1983 (Box 236)
    - Poem and artwork by Glenda Ervin (Box 236)
    - Glass hologram of Steinem (Box 237)
    - Pastel sketch of Steinem by Barbara Nessim, undated (Map-case Flat File)
    - University of Toledo photo collage, 1993 (Map-case Flat File)
    - Posters (Map-case Flat File)
    - Framed oil portrait of Steinem by Ming Ji Zhang (in office), 1990